dealguaranty.com 2015-06-15

# PRIVACY POLICY - dealguaranty

**Our Privacy Policy page**

Please read our Privacy policy statement carefully for all the latest information about our privacy plans and strategies. This privacy statement describes about how we use the information of those who use our DealGuaranty website or any other website links that are displayed on our website.

By using the Site, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Statement. If you do not agree with the points described in this Privacy Policy Statement, please do not share any of your personal information or interact with the site.

We will frequently update our Privacy policy statement, whenever we add new services, functionality or features to the Site. We will notify you by email.

**Information we collect**

We collect your information when you access or use the site, when you register, subscribe or when you create an account, open and reply to your emails, provide any information to register and participate in the programs with DealGuaranty. We also collect your information when you purchase products or services on or through the Site, visit any page online that displays our ads or content, post comments and provide information to our merchants.

**How we use your information**

We at DealGuaranty uses your information whenever we provide you some information about the offers on our products and services, and whenever we operate, maintain and improve our site its services. We use your information to complete the orders placed on the site, to reply with the feedback to your queries. To send some of the reminders, updates and alerts. And also whenever we do conducts contests and do surveys.

**How we collect your information**

We collect your personal information whenever you create an account by registering yourself and subscribe for a deal, purchase or redeem coupons, and sometimes during your interaction with the site. We at DealGuaranty will use such information as per the applicable laws. Provisionally, we use Cookies and session cookies in order to manage the pages on the site and to monitor the site activity.

** ** **Removing your personal information**

You can delete your information you provided to us in your profile by logging into your account or by sending us an email at [privacy@dealguaranty.com](mailto:privacy@dealguaranty.com).

If you want to close your DealGuaranty account or have other questions or requests, please contact us. We will help you in managing your account by closing it and deleting your profile.

**Social Networks**

The website is also accessible through certain social media sites where can able to post and share some information with others such as discussion boards or blogs, review products and merchants. We recommend not to post any personal information.

**Privacy of Third parties**

Our Privacy policy is applicable to all those who use our site. Other websites that may be accessible through links from our website may have their own privacy statements.

Our Business Partners may also have their own privacy statements. We recommend you to read the privacy statements provided by these other parties before providing them with information or taking interest in some of their sponsored offers and promotions.
